export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is React used for?",
      option1: "Front-end development",
      option2: "Server-side scripting",
      option3: "Database management",
      option4: "Mobile App development",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is JSX?",
      option1: "JavaScript XML",
      option2: "HTML",
      option3: "CSS",
      option4: "JSON",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What does React use to manage state?",
      option1: "Flux",
      option2: "Redux",
      option3: "Context API",
      option4: "setState",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "How do you create a React component?",
      option1: "class",
      option2: "function",
      option3: "span",
      option4: "div",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How can you pass data to a child component in React?",
      option1: "Redux",
      option2: "Context",
      option3: "State",
      option4: "Props",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the virtual DOM?",
      option1: "Direct Object Model",
      option2: "Document Object Model",
      option3: "Virtual Representation",
      option4: "JavaScript Object Model",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "How can you conditionally render components in React?",
      option1: "Using the ternary operator",
      option2: "Using the if-else statement",
      option3: "Using the switch case statement",
      option4: "Using the for loop",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is React Router used for?",
      option1: "State management",
      option2: "Server-side rendering",
      option3: "Navigation in React applications",
      option4: "Component styling",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What does Redux offer in React applications?",
      option1: "State management",
      option2: "Component styling",
      option3: "Routing",
      option4: "HTTP request",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which method is used to prevent the default behavior of an event in React?",
      option1: "preventDefault()",
      option2: "stopPropagation()",
      option3: "haltEvent()",
      option4: "cancelEvent()",
      ans: 1,
    },
  ];